http://www.synagogue.org.uk/privacy-policy/

Facilities Hire
Call us:
Belsize
Square Synagogue (BSS) is committed to safeguarding the privacy of our members,
service users and website visitors.
The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) requires BSS to explain how personal and/or private data that we collect will be processed.
What does this policy cover?
This Privacy Policy applies only to your use of our website. Our site contains links to other websites and also contains content embedded from other websites. Please note that we have no control over how your data is collected, stored, or used by other websites and we advise you to check the privacy policies of any such websites before providing any data to them.
How we collect data and who is it shared with?
Our website collects data using three methods:
Contact Us Page – the user provides personal information including their name, telephone number and email address. This information will be handled and stored by BSS employees or members of BSS who are responsible for an event/activity. The data will not be shared with third parties. Debit and credit card transactions – In order to process card transactions our payment provider collects data for verification with a bank or card processing agency. Google Analytics – A web analytics service provided by Google. Google Analytics uses ‘cookies’, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyse how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser; however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website.
Your rights
You have the right to request a copy of any information we currently hold about you, or to have your information deleted from our records. Contact the synagogue office to make the request.
If you believe your data has been mishandled, complaints can be made to Lee Taylor in the synagogue office. If you are dissatisfied you can make a formal complaint to the Information Commissioner’s Office.
Changes to Our Privacy Policy
We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time (for example, if the law changes). Any changes will be immediately posted on our site and you will be deemed to have accepted the terms of the Privacy Policy on your first use of our site following the alterations. We recommend that you check this page regularly to keep up-to-date.
Shabbat Service Times
Friday 18:45
Saturday 10:00
The Belsize Square Synagogue is a charity registered in England and Wales as a company limited by guarantee. Charity No: 1144866 - Company No: 7831243.
About
Privacy Policy
Join Us
Contact Us
Facilities Hire
51 Belsize Square London NW3 4HX020 - 7794 3949office@synagogue.org.uk
© 2015 Belsize Square Synagogue. All rights reserved.
This website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Cookie settingsACCEPTCookies overview
Close
Cookies Overview
This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyse and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Please click here to view our Privacy Policy in full, which includes more detail about how cookies are used.
Necessary
Necessary
Always Enabled
Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on a website.
